You are going to see a different Ravanna.
All in all, Ravanna has become a hit as we expected,
brother. That is, our mass
Maharaj Ravi Teja's Irumudi movie. Just
watch it now. Don't think for a second about how the movie is.
Go and watch it immediately. The movie is
not ordinary. It is really amazing. And this movie is going to be
one of the best movies in Ravi Teja's career
.  Ravana Thirunatha
lived up to his character and Priya
Bhavani also impressed with her natural acting
.  And Baby Nakshatra
dominated with her very cute acting.
And Shiva Nirvana connected the
audience emotionally with his change of direction
.  And it must be said that GV Prakash
has put the movie in a range with the BGM
.  The first half of the movie has a classy
and emotional touch.  The
pre-climax climax that comes in the second half from the interval is
pure
rampage.  No
one will sit in the seat for the song Mallepula Pallake, but
overall the movie is on a different level.
Comment how you felt.